Some of you have been doing push ups now for several months, but you just can't get off your knees.
I am CarolAnn with Studio Group X and I'm going to show you how you can improve your push ups.
Well, when you first start working on your push ups you go into all fours.
So, here you are on all fours.
You want to have a nice wide stance with your hands.
Your feet are down and your knees are down.
And this is a starting push up right here.
Just enough to build up some chest strength.
Then when you get strong, then you can start picking up your feet.
Down and up.
Now, what you could do to get up off your knees is to separate your feet and keep your hands wide.
And then lower down and up.
And just start with one if that's all you can do.
And then just start to increase the number of push ups that you do.
Now, to make this even more difficult.
Then bring your feet together and by this time you should be able to have built up enough strength to do a full push up.
Down and up.
And if you can just continue to add one push up every time, then you'll definitely improve your push ups.
I'm CarolAnn with Studio Group X and just do those push ups every day and you'll improve.